https://www.imrtest.com/updated-privacy-policy

Introduction
This site is provided as a service to our customers. Please review the following basic rules that govern your use of our Site (the "Agreement"). Please note that your use of our site constitutes your unconditional agreement to follow and be bound by these Terms and Conditions. Although you may "bookmark" a particular portion of this site and thereby bypass this Agreement, your use of this site still binds you to the Terms.
Curtiss-Wright Surface Technologies (“CWST”) reserves the right to update or modify these Terms and Conditions at any time without prior notice. Your use of the www.imrtest.com website following any such change constitutes your unconditional agreement to follow and be bound by the Terms and Conditions as changed. For this reason, we encourage you to review these Terms and Conditions whenever you use this website.
CWST is committed to protecting your privacy when you use our online resources or other services (“Services”) or when you request services from us, and we perform those services.  The objective of this policy is to explain how and why we collect, process and utilize your personal information.  In addition, we will describe how and why we share it, as well as the controls you, as the customer (“Customer”) have over our use of that data.  When you see the words ‘we’ or ‘us’ or ‘CWST” it means Curtiss-Wright Surface Technologies and its affiliated companies (including IMR Test Labs).
Occasionally, and as data privacy regulations evolve, we may review this policy and make appropriate addendums.  You will find these changes in the content of this Privacy Statement on this webpage.
Sharing your Information with Our International Business Units
There are times when we will need to transfer your personal information to other business units and technology groups within the CWST entity (including IMR Test Labs).  The primary purpose of this is to provide you with our services in the most efficient manner possible.  We may also utilize third-party vendors to process personal information when needed in relation to services they provide CWST.  Because of this, your personal information may end up being transferred to other countries where privacy laws may be different.  We assess these vendors acutely to insure our satisfaction with their corporate levels of privacy protection.
Use of this Website
This Site and all its Contents are intended solely for personal, non-commercial use. You may download or copy the Contents and other downloadable materials displayed on the Website for your personal use only. No right, title or interest in any downloaded materials or software is transferred to you as a result of any such downloading or copying.
You may not reproduce (except as noted above), publish, transmit, distribute, display, modify, create derivative works from, sell or participate in any sale of or exploit in any way, in whole or in part, any of the Contents, the Site or any related software. All software used on this site is the property of CWST or its suppliers and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws.
The content and software on this site may be used only as a reference resource. Any other use, including the reproduction, modification, distribution, transmission, republication, display, or performance, of the content on this site is strictly prohibited.
Site Security
Users are prohibited from violating or attempting to violate the security of the Site, including, without limitation, (a) accessing data not intended for such user or logging onto a server or an account which the user is not authorized to access; (b) attempting to probe, scan or test the vulnerability of a system or network or to breach security or authentication measures without proper authorization; (c) attempting to interfere with service to any user, host or network, including, without limitation, via means of submitting a virus to the Site, overloading, "flooding," "spamming," "mailbombing" or "crashing;" (d) sending unsolicited email, including promotions and/or advertising of products or services; or (e) forging any TCP/IP packet header or any part of the header information in any email or newsgroup posting. Violations of system or network security may result in civil or criminal liability.
The Company will investigate occurrences that may involve such violations and may involve, and cooperate with, law enforcement authorities in prosecuting users who are involved in such violations. You agree not to use any device, software or routine to interfere or attempt to interfere with the proper working of this Site or any activity being conducted on this site. You agree, further, not to use or attempt to use any engine, software, tool, agent or other device or mechanism (including without limitation browsers, spiders, robots, avatars or intelligent agents) to navigate or search this Site other than the search engine and search agents available from Company on this Site and other than generally available third party web browsers (e.g., Microsoft Explorer, FireFox, Google,Chrome).
Other Websites
The websites for CWST and its associated companies (including IMR Test Labs) often contain links to third party sites, who’s content, security and policies we do not control.  This privacy statement relates only to CWST websites, and we don’t accept any responsibility or liability for websites not under our control.  We encourage you to review every website’s privacy policy before deciding to share your personal information.  The links provided on our websites aren’t intended to, and do not imply, an endorsement of any kind.  Any links to CWST websites must be requested (and approved by us) in writing before activation.
Why We Retain Your Personal Information
We will keep your information on file if required for the various reasons below.  These reasons will comply with current data protection regulations and when your data is no longer required for these reasons, we will destroy it.
Marketing
To keep our customers informed about relevant Products and Services we offer, or additional capabilities and newsworthy items, we occasionally send letters, make phone calls or send emails. To unsubscribe from any of these marketing-related communications, follow the unsubscribe link provided in every email, call us at +1 607-533-7000, or email us at sales@imrtest.com.
Cookies
CWST and its associated companies (including IMR Test Labs) utilize cookies to improve your experience with our websites.  These cookies identify your unique address and helps us identify your preferred pages when you visit.  You can change these delivery of these cookies by adjusting your web browser’s settings to block or delete cookies.  This action may result in some loss of functionality on the website.
What Personal Information is Collected, and Why?
When we collect your personal information in relation to the use of our Services, the data we retain includes your name, company, business sector, address, email address and phone number.
The Legal Basis and Purpose of Your Collected Information
LEGAL BASIS
PURPOSE
Necessary Pre-Contract or Pre-Service Activities
To respond to customer requests for information and pricing on information on our Services
To review and process employment application
To review and process Products or Services supplied to IMR
Performance of Contract
To provide our Services to customer
To review and improve our Services
To help and support customer in using Services
Legitimate Interests
To provide Services to customer
To review and improve our Services
To confirm, update and improve customer records
To review, develop and improve customer relationships
To inform customers about changes and improvements to IMR website
To customize and improve customer website experience
In relation to credit cards and related services
To inform customers about related and relevant Services
For other reasons related to our business operations
Legal Obligations
To confirm, update and improve customer records
To review, develop and improve customer relationships
To inform customers about changes and improvements to IMR website
To customize and improve customer website experience
In relation to credit cards and related services
With Customer Consent
To keep customer informed of other relevant Services
Any other reason to which customer consents
How and When Your Information Might Be Shared
There may be instances when we need to share your personal data.  These are generally limited to aiding us in providing our Services to you.  These may include (but aren’t limited to):
Other CWST business units or technology groups (including IMR Test Labs).
Our third party service providers who process information on our behalf to provide our Services or to run some of our internal business operations including email distribution, IT services, business support and customer services;
Law enforcement organizations in order to comply with any legal obligation or court order.
Security of Your Personal Information
CWST takes the importance of securing our customers personal information very seriously.  We invest dollars, people and resources to insure the protection of your data.  As such, we review and improve our policies regarding privacy and security frequently.  We only allow authorized personnel to have access to your personal information.
Unfortunately, no internet-based website can insure 100% security.  CWST cannot be held responsible for unauthorized or unintended access to our websites that is unforeseen or beyond our control.  We will take every precaution to protect your personal information, but cannot guarantee the safekeeping of any data that is sent via internet or email.
Your Rights
If you would like to request copies of the personal information held by us and how we use it, please contact us in writing at the address below.  We will promptly make any changes to any incorrect or outdated data you make us aware of.
You may also request for us to stop collecting your personal information and withdraw your consent.  This request may not apply if there are legal reasons for continuing to use your data.
Complaints Process
If you have a complaint about how we have handled your personal information you may contact us at IMR Test Labs, 131 Woodsedge Drive, Lansing, NY 14882, and we will investigate your complaint.
Copyright Statement
Unless otherwise noted, all materials, including images, text, illustrations, designs, icons, photographs, programs, video clips and written and other materials that are part of this Site (collectively, the "Contents") are copyrights, trademarks, trade dress and/or other intellectual property owned, controlled or licensed by Curtiss-Wright, one of its affiliates or by third parties who have licensed their materials to Curtiss-Wright and are protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. The compilation (meaning the collection, arrangement, and assembly) of all content on this site is the exclusive property of Curtiss-Wright and is also protected by U.S. and international copyright laws.
Curtiss-Wright and its suppliers and licensors expressly reserve all intellectual property rights in all text, programs, products, processes, technology, content and other materials which appear on this website. Access to this website does not confer and shall not be considered as conferring upon anyone any license under any of Curtiss-Wright's or any third party's intellectual property rights.
The Curtiss-Wright names and logos and all related product and service names, design marks and slogans are the trademarks or service marks of Curtiss-Wright. All other marks are the property of their respective companies. No trademark or service mark license is granted in connection with the materials contained on this website. Access to this website does not authorize anyone to use any name, logo or mark in any manner.
References on this website to any names, marks, products or services of third parties or hypertext links to third party sites or information are provided solely as a convenience to you and do not in any way constitute or imply Curtiss-Wright's endorsement, sponsorship or recommendation of the third party, information, product or service. Curtiss-Wright is not responsible for the content of any third party sites and does not make any representations regarding the content or accuracy of material on such sites. If you decide to link to any such third party web sites, you do so entirely at your own risk.
Analytical Services
Chemical Analysis
Coating Evaluation
Corrosion Testing
Failure Analysis
Mechanical Testing
Metallurgical Analysis
Nonmetallics Testing
Curtiss-Wright Divisions:
